<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
	  "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<bknr:toplevel
   template="toplevel_main"
   title="RAINFOREST for SAMBOJA LESTARI"
   xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
   xmlns:bknr="http://bknr.net"
   xmlns:bos="http://headcraft.de/bos"
   >
  <bos:set-cachable/>
  <div class="slim-body with-left-bar">
    <h1>Reforestation completed</h1>
    <h2>10 years Samboja Lestari - Thank you for your support!</h2>
    <div class="right">
      <object classid="clsid:d27cdb6e-ae6d-11cf-96b8-444553540000"
              codebase="http://fpdownload.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=8,0,0,0"
              width="190" height="205" id="schafft_lebenswald" align="middle">
        <param name="allowScriptAccess" value="sameDomain" />
        <param name="movie" value="schafft_lebenswald.swf" />
        <param name="quality" value="high" /><param name="bgcolor" value="#ffffff" />
        <embed src="/static/schafft_lebenswald.swf" quality="high" bgcolor="#ffffff" width="190"
               height="205" name="schafft_lebenswald" align="middle" allowScriptAccess="sameDomain"
               type="application/x-shockwave-flash" pluginspage="http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer" />
      </object>
    </div>
    <p>
      A large number of donors have helped to reforest Samboja
      Lestari. Ten years ago the area was still predominantly
      overgrown with the nutrient-poor, all dominating, alang-alang
      grass (Imperata cylindrica) With the new trees, the micro
      climate, soil structure and water balance have improved
      significantly. The newly formed layer of vegetation can store
      water more efficiently, making it available in the dry season
      and reducing the risk of flooding during the rainy season.
    </p>
    <p>
      The biodiversity has also increased once more. Among the trees
      planted were included species which had died out in the
      wild. Observations show also that more and more species of
      animals are colonizing the area again. Through reforestation a
      state was reached over a period of ten years, which would have
      taken decades to develop on its own.
    </p>
    <p>
      The tree planting in Samboja Lestari is now practically
      complete. Nearly 1,200 acres have been planted with over half a
      million trees and over 400 species, 413 hectares will be left to
      natural development. The school is comprised of 75 hectares of
      forest and the arboretum is 18 hectares. Then there is the sun
      bear enclosure and the orangutan islands, each with 58 and 7
      acres.  In Samboja Lestari degraded land could be successfully
      restored to its natural state. Nevertheless, the protection of
      virgin rainforests comes first and foremost! Reforestation is
      time-consuming, expensive and labour-consuming and can never
      replace the value of a million years old, original
      forest. That's why it is important for BOS Foundation to acquire
      conservation concessions for <a href="#"
      onclick="javascript:window_extra('kehje-sewen')">intact rain
      forest</a> areas from the Indonesian government and to
      facilitate their preservation, since it is only in extensive,
      original or very natural forests that orangutans can
      successfully reproduce and survive.
    </p>
  </div>
</bknr:toplevel>
