<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
	"http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<bknr:toplevel
  template="toplevel_main"
  title="RAINFOREST for SAMBOJA LESTARI"
  xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
  xmlns:bknr="http://bknr.net"
  xmlns:bos="http://headcraft.de/bos"
  >
  <bos:set-cachable/>
	<!-- container content_main -->
	<div id="content_main">
		<div id="textbox_content_bigger">
			<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0">
				<tr>
					<td colspan="2">
						<span class="headline">
							Orangutan, Sunbear and Rhinoceros bird 
						</span>
					</td>
					<td align="center" valign="top">
						<img src="/images/pfeil_back.gif" width="10" height="9" alt="" />
						<a href="#" onclick="history.back()" class="titlegray">
							back
						</a>
				  	</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
					<td><img src="/images/trans.gif" width="120" height="15" alt="" /></td>
					<td><img src="/images/trans.gif" width="130" height="10" alt="" /></td>
					<td width="150"><img src="/images/trans.gif" width="140" height="10" alt="" /></td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
					<td colspan="3">
						Orangutans, also called man of the forest, are highly endangered great apes.
						<br /><br />
						Orangutans are not only our closest relatives in the animal kingdom; they are also indispensable for the biological diversity 
						of the rainforest due to their role of seed distributors. They are the so called umbrella species. The protection of these fascinating 
						great apes serves at the same time to preserve the rainforest's eco system.
						<br /><br />
						Nowadays, orangutans live only on Sumatra and Borneo. Massive rainforest destruction and unscrupulous pet trade could 
						mean the end of their species. Sunbears are also in danger of losing their natural habitat. The nature reserve Samboja Lestari represents  
refuge for several species of animals - a chance for their survival.  52 sunbears  are already living in  a specially confined area.  Infected orang-utans, unfit for realease, 
live on artificial islands. In  the forest school young orang-utans train for their future release
						<br /><br />
						Rare species such as the Rhinoceros bird, the dwarf deer and the king cobra can already be observed in Samboja Lestari nowadays.
 					</td>
				</tr>
				<tr><td height="50"></td></tr>		
				<tr>
					<td valign="top" colspan="3">
						<img src="/images/pic_h3_orangutan.jpg" width="169" height="88" border="0" alt="" />
						<img src="/images/pic_h3_baer.jpg" width="169" height="88" border="0" alt="" />
						<img src="/images/pic_h3_vogel.jpg" width="169" height="88" alt="" />
					</td>
				</tr>			
				<tr><td height="20"></td></tr>	
			</table>	
		</div>	
	</div><!-- /container content_main -->
</bknr:toplevel>
