<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
"http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<bknr:toplevel
    template="toplevel_main"
    title="RAINFOREST for SAMBOJA LESTARI"
    xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
    xmlns:bknr="http://bknr.net"
    xmlns:bos="http://headcraft.de/bos"
    >
  <bos:set-cachable/>
  <div class="slim-body with-left-bar">
    <h1>The local population</h1>
    <img class="right" src="/images/headline3-picture.jpg" width="400" height="267" border="0" alt=""></img>
    <p>
      Since the beginning of the project care has been taken to
      involve the local population in the projects. Virtually all
      employees are from the area. In this way, the project has been
      accepted and throughout the last ten years has been able to
      create jobs, many of which still exist today. Local farmers
      planted the trees while others produce compost, work in the
      Eco-lodge or for fire protection, care for the orangutans and
      sun bears. Through the principal of agro forestry local farmers
      have the opportunity to cultivate their crops between the
      planted trees The yield helps feed the orangutans. Thus all
      parties work hand in hand for mutual benefit. At the same time
      the use of agriculture prevents the dominant alang-alang grass
      from suffocating and displacing the young seedlings.
    </p>
    <p>
      As always the orangutans and sun bears in Samboja Lestari
      consume huge quantities of fruit and vegetables, which, whenever
      possible, is purchased from local farmers.  Additionally,it was
      possible to improve the agricultural methods of the peasants
      with training Thus, the harrowing of the fields as an
      alternative to the standard practice of burning crop residues or
      alang-alang grass were demonstrated, thus helping to counter the
      arising of uncontrolled fires.
    </p>
  </div>
</bknr:toplevel>
