<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
	"http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<bknr:toplevel
  template="toplevel_main"
  title="RAINFOREST for SAMBOJA LESTARI"
  xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
  xmlns:bknr="http://bknr.net"
  xmlns:bos="http://headcraft.de/bos"
  >
	<!-- container content_main -->
	<div id="content_main">
		<div id="textbox_content_bigger">
			<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0">
				<tr>
					<td colspan="2">
						<span class="headline">
							Agriculture, reforestation and protection
 <br /> - a good combination
						</span>
					</td>
					<td align="center"><img src="/images/pfeil_back.gif" width="10" height="9" alt="" />
						<a href="javascript:history.back()" class="titlegray">
							back
						</a>
					</td>		
				</tr>
				<tr>
					<td height="6" width="150"><img src="/images/trans.gif" width="160" height="6" alt="" /> </td>
					<td><img src="/images/trans.gif" width="150" height="6" alt="" /></td>
					<td width="150"><img src="/images/trans.gif" width="150" height="6" alt="" /></td>
				</tr>				
				<tr>
					<td align="left"><img src="/images/pic_headline1b_big.jpg" width="149" height="180" alt="" border="0" /></td>
					<td colspan="2">
During the early stage of reforestion Indonesian farmers plant profitable agricultural products among the newly planted trees.
					<br /><br />
Agriculture and reforestation influence each other in many positive ways: agricultural products protect the young tropical trees from getting overgrown by elephant grass. Trees enrich the quality of the soil and provide shade.
					<br /><br />
BOS guarantees to buy fruit like papaya and pineapples from the farmers, market them regionally or use them for self-supply. The supply of the orangutans in Wanariset rehabilitation center alone takes about 1000 kg of fruit daily. 
					</td>
					<td></td>			
				</tr>
				<tr><td height="6"></td></tr>
				<tr>
					<td colspan="3">				
					</td>			
				</tr>	
				<tr><td height="6"> </td></tr>
				<tr>
					<td colspan="2"><span class="headline">The Protection (circle)</span></td>
					<td rowspan="3">

						<img src="/images/ring_en.jpg" width="215" height="150" border="0" alt="" />
					</td>
				</tr>
				<tr><td height="6"> </td></tr>
				<tr>
					<td colspan="2">

 A <img src="/images/pfeil_link_on.gif" width="10" height="9" alt="" /> <a  href="javascript:window_ringdetail();"
class="content_green">circle of sugar-palm plantations</a> is being planted all around the nature reserve. Over 650 families will profit from the main product sugar. And - the circle forms a barrier against the much feared forest fires.
					<br /><br />
A penetration of humans into the nature reserve, as well as the breakout of orangutans is prevented by an inner protection wall of thickly growing, prickly salac palms. Moreover, the fruit of these palms provides pleasant tasting food for humans and animals.
					</td>
				</tr>
				<tr><td colspan="3">
Ultra-light aeroplanes and modern satellite technique support the permanent surveillance of the BOS projects. Thus, slash-and-burn and illegal logging can be fought much more effectively. 
					</td>
				</tr>	
			</table>		
		</div>	
	</div>	
</bknr:toplevel>