<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
	"http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<bknr:toplevel
  template="toplevel_main"
  title="RAINFOREST for SAMBOJA LESTARI"
  xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
  xmlns:bknr="http://bknr.net"
  xmlns:bos="http://headcraft.de/bos"
  >
  <bos:set-cachable/>
	<div id="content_main">
		<div id="textbox_content_bigger">
			<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0">
				<tr>
					<td colspan="2"><span class="headline">A square metre with a certain knack <br /></span></td>
					<td align="center">
						<img src="/images/pfeil_back.gif" width="10" height="9" alt="" />
						<a href="#" onclick="history.back()" class="titlegray">
							back
						</a>
					</td>		
				</tr>
				<tr><td height="16"> </td>
				</tr>	
				<tr>			
					<td colspan="3">
						To finance the nature reserve, BOS has created a system of symbolical land-purchasing.
						<br /><br />
						<a href="bestellung" class="titlered">
							For 3 Euros per m² you can help creating rainforest.
						</a> 
						<br /><br />
					</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
					<td colspan="2">
						You help financing the purchase of land, ecological reforestation, a nursery, ecological agriculture, sugar palm plantations, wages for Indonesian employees, surveillance and protection of the area, fire fighting, environmental education, infrastructure, research and arboretum, orangutan islands and sunbear areas.
						<br /><br />
Contribute to a better future and observe the development of the Samboja Lestari project on the internet.
					</td>
					<td>
						<img src="/images/projekt_pic_en.jpg" width="240" height="120" />
					</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
					<td colspan="3">
						<br />
						Each square metre that you purchase symbolically will be assigned to you by a personal profile. Via a password you will be able to re-find your squaremeters easily at any time. It is also possible to place short informations on 'your' m² and thus communicate with other Samboja Lestari sponsors.
Visitors of this website will be able to gain insight into all m² and their personal profiles.
						<br /><br />
						<b>Observe the development of 'your' area from different perspectives. BOS provides a transparent insight via satellite pictures, and gives regular reports about the progress in situ.</b>
						<br /><br />
						Support the project and receive a rainforest document. You can also give squaremeters as a present to friends, relatives and other people you know.
						<br /><br />
						Participate and see rainforest grow! - And much more! 
					</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
					<td height="6"> 
					</td>
				</tr>				
			</table>	
		</div>	
	</div>
	<!-- /container content_main -->
</bknr:toplevel>
