<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
"http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<bknr:toplevel
    template="toplevel_main"
    title="RAINFOREST for SAMBOJA LESTARI"
    xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
    xmlns:bknr="http://bknr.net"
    xmlns:bos="http://headcraft.de/bos"
    >
  <bos:set-cachable/>
  <div class="slim-body with-left-bar">
    <h1>10 Jahre Samboja Lestari</h1>
    <p>
      <img src="/images/startseite-oben.jpg" width="364" height="120" alt="" border="0" />
    </p>
    <p>
      Samboja Lestari is a 1850 hectare area in East Kalimantan, a
      province in the Indonesian part of Borneo. Through logging and
      fires it was downgraded to a nutrient-poor grassland. Over the
      past ten years BOS Foundation has succeeded in turning the land
      back into a species-rich habitat through reforestation and fire
      protection.
    </p>
    <p>
      Today a rescue and rehabilitation station is being run for
      orangutans and sun bears in Samboja Lestari. The first
      reintroductions of orangutans from Samboja Lestari to <a
      href="javascript:window_extra('kehje-sewen')">appropriate areas
      of rainforest</a> are planned for 2012. In order to survive in
      freedom, our red-headed relatives receive training in the forest
      school of Samboja Lestari and are given a thorough health
      examination.  Some animals are too ill or too disturbed for
      re-introduction. For this reason enclosures which enable them to
      lead a dignified life need to be built and maintained.  A few
      islands surrounded by moats also offer the sick and disabled
      orangutans a permanent place to live.
    </p>
    <p>
      Today BOS Foundation's work in Samboja Lestari is focused on the
      preservation of the area and taking care of the animals.  <a
      href="/de/bestellung" class="spenden">Help the orangutans and
      sun bears through the acquisition of symbolic square metres in
      Samboja Lestari!</a>
    </p>
  </div>
</bknr:toplevel>
