<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
	"http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<bknr:toplevel
  template="toplevel_extra"
  title="RAINFOREST for SAMBOJA LESTARI - Guide to the Satellite Map"
  xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
  xmlns:bknr="http://bknr.net"
  xmlns:bos="http://headcraft.de/bos"
  >
	<h1 class="extra">Guide to the Satellite Map</h1>
	<p class="text_content">
		<p> You are now in the map overview for the square metre sales area. 
		Here you can get an overview of how many square metres have already been sold. 
		In addition you can see the sponsors profiles and their posted messages. </p>
		<p> If you are logged on with your password your "own" square metres will be marked with an icon  (<img src="/images/qm.gif"
		border="0" />)on the satellite map. The "purchased" square metres will be highlighted in a different colour. 
		Click on the satellite map in the middle of the screen to move the "Square Metre Magnifier". 
		The red marked area will appear in an enlarged form in the upper right of the screen. Click on the "sold" 
		colour marked square metre areas in the enlarged image to find out more about the sponsors in their sponsor profile. 
		This is displayed under the enlarged area and is shown by moving the mouse over it. </p>
		<p> On the bottom right of the satellite map you can get the area menu. Click on the individual 
		areas on the satellite map to 
		get the names of the individual areas. </p>
		<p>The following areas can be viewed:</p>
		<p style="margin-left: 40px; margin-right: 40px;"> 
		  <bl>
		    <li><strong>Sat-Karte</strong> The satellite map is the background of the map  </li>
		    <li><strong>Areas for Sale</strong>Areas that can be purchased are shown in grey.  </li>
		    <li><strong>Sold Areas</strong> Areas that have been purchased are displayed in various colours</li>
		  </bl>
		</p>
		<p>Click on the overview map on the top left to return to the POI overview.</p>
	</p>
</bknr:toplevel>
