<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
	"http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<bknr:toplevel
  template="toplevel_extra"
  title="RAINFOREST for SAMBOJA LESTARI - Privacy Policy"
  xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
  xmlns:bknr="http://bknr.net"
  xmlns:bos="http://headcraft.de/bos"
  >
  <bos:set-cachable/>
	<h1 class="extra">Privacy Policy of BOS Deutschland e.V.</h1>
	<p class="text_content">
		<p>
The protection of your personal data via electronic processing is strictly regulated, 
and is something BOS Deutschland e.V. takes very seriously.BOS Deutschland e.V. (BOS Germany) is an officially registered and eligible 
not-for-profit society complying with the Bundesdatenschutzgesetz (German Privacy Policy Law).  
BOS Germany is officially registered under no. 502 VR 24216 B at the Amtsgericht (county court) Berlin Charlottenburg; exemption paper of 
the Finanzamt (tax office) in Kiel-Nord, no. GL5105.
		</p>
		<p>
<b>What happens with your personal data?</b>
		</p>
		<p>
Once you have decided to make a donation on-line, you are asked to disclose 
your bank details. This information will exclusively be processed by WorldPay. 
WorldPay is a renowned, international provider for on-line payment. 
Your data will be send by WorldPay through a coded SSL-transaction, 
and deleted immediately after the successful transaction. 
BOS Deutschand e.V. has no access to your bank details whatsoever.
		</p>
		<p>
Each square metre of the ecological project you sponsor with your donation 
is linked to your personal profile. This profile consists of your name, 
country of origin, number of square metres you sponsor and the date of your donation. 
A personalised greeting text is possible. All profile information (except your e-mail address and postal address) 
is available to visitors of our webpage. Through this, transparency and interaction between sponsors is being promoted. Profile information can be altered by logging in with your password at all times. 
By doing so, it is also possible to stay anonymous.
		</p>
		<p>
In order to send you your personal profile including your sponsor-ID and password, we need your e-mail address. 
For sending certificates by mail we need your postal address, and the name of the person the certificate is 
to be issued to. 
In order to receive our newsletter/news we would need your e-mail address.
		</p>
		<p>
We assure you that this data will only be used for administrative and informative  
purposes of BOS Deutschland e.V.,as well as for BOS associates international. 
In case you do not wish to receive any more information from us, you are able to 
delete your data from the system at any time. 
For this purpose, please always give your sponsor ID!
		</p>
		<p>
In case you have further questions regarding the reglementation of privacy policy of BOS Deutschland e.V., 
please send an e-mail to: datenschutz@bos-deutschland.de
		</p>
	</p>
</bknr:toplevel>
