<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
	"http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<bknr:toplevel
  template="toplevel_extra"
  title="RAINFOREST for SAMBOJA LESTARI - Guide to the Satellite Map"
  xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
  xmlns:bknr="http://bknr.net"
  xmlns:bos="http://headcraft.de/bos"
  >
	<h1 class="extra">About the satellite map</h1>
	<p class="text_content">
		<p> You find yourself in our satellite information system. Here you can see for yourself 
		how the project area in Samboja Lestari looks like. 
		Furthermore, you can look up where the square metres you have sponsored are located.  </p>
		<p>
		On the main map you see several icons you can click at, which will then lead you to further images:</p>
		<span style="border-left:30px; border-right:30px">
			<table border="0">
				<tr>
					<td width="20"> </td>
					<td>
						<img src="/images/punkt.gif" border="0" />
					</td>
					<td>
						Here is one facility run by BOS.
					</td>
					<td width="20"> </td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
					<td width="20"> </td>
					<td>
						<img src="/images/palme.gif" border="0" />
					</td>
					<td>
						This icon marks a point of interest in the project area.
					</td>
					<td width="20"> </td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
					<td width="20"> </td>
					<td>
						<img src="/images/sale.gif" border="0" />
					</td>
					<td>
						Sales area for square metres. Here, profiles of square metre sponsors can be looked at. 
					</td>
					<td width="20"> </td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
					<td width="20"> </td>
					<td>
						<img src="/images/qm.gif" border="0" />
					</td>
					<td>
						Here are 'your' square metres. This icon only comes up if you are registered. 
					</td>
					<td width="20"> </td>
				</tr>
			</table>
		</span>
		<p> By clicking at the 'point of interest' list on the left, 
		    you will get directly to the point of interest you wish to look at. </p>
		<p> In order to get back to the main menu from one of the sublevels, 
		    please click at the main map on the top left. </p>
		<p> In case you already have sponsored square metres, you can register on the bottom left 
		    by entering your sponsor-ID, password or mastercode into the login-area. You then have access 
		    to your sponsor profile. You are able to recall your sponsor status; 
		    and you have access to your rainforest-certificate as PDF document. </p>
		<p> We wish you lots of fun on your virtual expedition to Samboja Lestari!</p>
	</p>					
</bknr:toplevel>
